

Sergi Monzó

Game Programmer

Details

sergimonzoareste@gmail.com

券 <u>https://linktr.ee/sergimonzo</u>

Hard Skills

C#

Clean Code

Design Patterns

Software Architecture

Unity

Version Control

Soft Skills

Collaboration & Teamwork

Organisation

Fast learner

Proactive

Problem solver

Languages

English Full Professional Proficiency

Spanish Native

Catalan Native

About me

I'm a Game Developer (Gameplay Programmer) with over 7 years of experience developing projects for PC and consoles. Currently, I am working at Level Up Game Studios as a freelance Game Programmer.

At present, I specialise in Unity and C#, although I also have experience in other programming languages. Moreover, I always apply clean code architecture, using Clean Code, Design Patterns, and SOLID principles. Because I like to constantly renew myself, I am also learning new skills, such as C++ and Unreal Engine.

Furthermore, I am a lover of challenges, which is why I frequently participate in Game Jams and long-term projects.

Experience

Game Programmer

Level Up Game Studios ● Barcelona - Remote

June 2024 - Present

- Writing clean, efficient code for game mechanics and features
- Refining game functionality and enhancing the player experience

Game Programmer

Barcelona - Remote HidBox Games

September 2021 - Present

- Writing clean, efficient code for game mechanics and features
- Refining game functionality and enhancing the player experience

Game Programmer

Questmasters Barcelona - Onsite

iii October 2020 - March 2021

• Implemented gameplay features that enriched the player experience

Education

Advanced Videogame Programming with Unity

Level Up [Game Dev Hub] • Barcelona - Remote

m April 2023 - October 2023

(300 hours

- Enhanced my C# and Unity skills from Intermediate to Advanced
- Gained in-depth knowledge of clean code principles
- Mastered design patterns and software architecture

3D Animations, Games and Interactive Environments

Barcelona - Onsite

Institut Mare de Déu de la Mercè

(2000 hours

September 2019 - June 2021

• Enhanced my C# and Unity skills from Basic to Intermediate

Multiplatform Application Development

Sabadell - Onsite IES Sabadell

September 2015 - June 2018

(2000 hours

• Learned C# and Unity skills to Basic